junglescout.com 2019-03-02

# Privacy Policy | Jungle Scout: Amazon Product Research Made Easy

**Jungle Scout Privacy Policy  
**_Last Updated February 3rd, 2016_

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, Jungle Scout collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Jungle Scout’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Jungle Scout’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Jungle Scout may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Jungle Scout also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our blog. Jungle Scout only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that blog commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog where the comment was left.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to Jungle Scout’s Website choose to interact with Jungle Scout in ways that require Jungle Scout to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Jungle Scout gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Those whom  engage in transactions with Jungle Scout are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Jungle Scout collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Jungle Scout. Jungle Scout does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**

Jungle Scout may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. Jungle Scout may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Jungle Scout does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

Jungle Scout discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Jungle Scout’s behalf or to provide services available at Jungle Scout’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Jungle Scout’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Jungle Scout will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Jungle Scout discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Jungle Scout believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Jungle Scout, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Jungle Scout website and have supplied your email address, Jungle Scout may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Jungle Scout and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Jungle Scout takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Jungle Scout uses cookies to help Jungle Scout identify and track visitors, their usage of Jungle Scout website, and their website access preferences. Jungle Scout visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Jungle Scout’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Jungle Scout’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Business Transfers**

If Jungle Scout, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Jungle Scout goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Jungle Scout may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

**Ads**

Any ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Jungle Scout and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Accessing and Correcting Your Information**

You can help ensure that your contact information and preferences are accurate, complete, and up to date by logging in to your account at www.junglescout.com. For other personal information we hold, we will provide you with access for any purpose including to request that we correct the data if it is inaccurate or delete the data if we are not required to retain it by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may decline to process requests that are frivolous/vexatious, jeopardize the privacy of others, are extremely impractical, or for which access is not otherwise required by local law.

**California Privacy Rights**

If you are a California resident, you may have certain additional rights. California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by us to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. California Business and Professions Code Section 22581 permits registered users who are minors to request and obtain deletion of certain posted content.

**Comments**

Comments and other content submitted to us are saved on our servers.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Jungle Scout may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Jungle Scout’s sole discretion. Jungle Scout encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or comments we may be reached at support at junglescout dot com.
